Hurry up with the water.
I'm steaming inside my own shell, I am.
It's that hot, it is.
Man, it's hot.
How hot is it?
It's so hot, I poured McDonald's coffee
in my lap to cool off.
Johnny Carson said it.
No, Nibbler!
Don't drink the pool water.
It's full of chlorine.
Ah.
Lightweights.
Oh, wait, chlorine.
Perhaps this movie
will help take our minds off the heat.
Focus.
You're probably wondering
why your ice cream went away.
Well, Susie, the culprit isn't foreigners.
It's global warming.
Gwobu wabu?
Yeah.
Meet Mr. Sunbeam.
He comes all the way
from the sun to visit Earth.
Hello, Earth.
Just popping in to brighten your day.
And now, I'll be on my way.
Not so fast, Sunbeam.
We're greenhouse gases.
You ain't going nowhere.
Oh, God, it hurts.
Pretty soon,
Earthis chock-full of sunbeams,
their rotting corpses
heating our atmosphere.
How do we get wid
of the gweenhouse gwases?
Fortunately, our handsomest politicians
came up with a cheap, last-minute way
to combat global warming.
Ever since 2063, we simply
drop a giant ice cube
into the ocean every now and then.
Just like Daddy puts
in his dwink every morning.
And then he gets mad.
Of course, since the greenhouse
gases are still building up,
it takes more and more ice each time.
Thus, solving the problem
once and for all.
- But...
- Once and for all!
Well, we just need one
of those big ice cubes.
Someone should call the losers
who were supposed to deliver it.
Hello?
President Nixon here.
I'm hiring you losers to deliver the ice.
And hurry up.
I'm sweating like J. Edgar Hoover
trying to squeeze into a new girdle.
You heard the good news, everyone.
Save the Earth, et cetera, et cetera.
Bye.
Wait, where do we get the ice?
The whuh?
Oh, Halley's Comet, of course.
The only sufficient source of ice cubes
that don't have bugs in them.
Wow, mining a comet. That sounds fun.
Yes, there's no safer occupation
than mining.
Especially when
you're perched on a snowball
whipping through space
at a million miles an hour.
Whoo, whoo, whoo.
Safe.
Deploying ice drill.
Wow, that ice dispenser's so big,
the ice crushes you.
Yakov Smirnoff said it.
No, he didn't.
Activating ice drill.
Oh, my God. It's out of ice.
Like some outer space Motel 6.
Completely out of ice?
This could mean
the end of the banana daiquiri
as we know it.
Also life.
With Halley's Comet out of ice,
Earth is experiencing
the devastating effects
of sudden, intense global warming.
Morbo is pleased but sticky.
The scorching heat has melted
the polar ice caps,
causing floods of Biblical proportion.
They called me crazy
for building this ark.
You are crazy.
You filled it with
same-sex animal couples.
Hey, there are parts of the Bible I like
and parts I don't like.
Direct your pity now
to the African turtles
seen here migrating
to cooler homes in Holland.
That poor turtle.
Bender, are you crying?
Uh, no, never.
Morbo wishes these stalwart nomads
peace amongst the Dutch tulips.
I'm sure those windmills
will keep them cool.
Windmills do not work that way!
Good night!
Well, everybody, I just saved a turtle.
What have you done with your lives?
You went all the way to Holland already?
Bender, a turtle isn't yourself.
Why do you care about it?
Because, I also care deeply about things
that remind me of myself.
Like poor little Shelly here.
What could you possibly have in common
with this walking soup mix?
For one thing,
we both have a tough outer shell.
But lead a rich inner life.
And also... Well, you know.
You're both alcoholic,
whoremongering, chain-smoking gamblers?
No, it's just...
Neither of us can get up
when we get knocked on our back.
What! I've seen you
get up off your back tons of times.
Those times I was slightly on my side.
Interesting.
Maybe we should test this
erectile dysfunction of yours, Bender.
Uh, no, that's not necessary, really.
I think I hear my factory recalling me.
Oh, that's what I get
for sharing my vulnerability with you.
Calling all scientists.
Be advised, there will be
a worldwide conference
on global warming in Kyōto, Japan.
I've got a degree in homeopathic medicine.
You've got a degree in baloney.
Professor Farnsworth, you're a scientist.
Forget it. I'm not going.
I have my reasons.
Shut up, all of you!
Strange.
You haven't acted this suspicious
since I found those
"ape" bones in the basement.
My hip hurts.
I'm in the middle of cooking a turkey.
I have warranty cards to fill out.
I am not just making excuses.
All right, I'll go!
I can't believe it! I love you!
Oh, oh, oh,
it's Professor Hubert Farnsworth.
He's looking sharp in a standard
white lab coat and dark slacks.
His wristwatch is a Casio.
Thank you all for coming.
It is my pleasure to introduce the host
of the Kyōto global warming convention.
The inventor of the environment,
and first Emperor of the Moon,
Al Gore.
I have ridden the mighty Moon worm.
Good for him.
My fellow Earthicans,
as I discuss in my book,
Earth in the Balance,
and the much more popular
Harry Patter and the Balance of Earth,
we need to defend our planet
against pollution
as well as dark wizards.
Sure, blame the wizards.
That's why I'm offering
a bag of Moon sapphires
to the first scientist
who can solve this problem
once and for all.
Lovely, aren't they?
Sapphires?
With those I could open
the Gate of Garesh.
First up is Professor Ogden Wernstrom.
Wernstrom!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have placed in orbit a giant mirror
that will reflect 40% of the sun's rays,
thus cooling Earth.
Observe.
Problem solved.
Whoa.
That's a little bright.
All right...
What else we got?
Professor, you're a professor.
You must have some ideas.
Absolutely not.
I won't speak. I've got nothing to hide!
Our next speaker is Professor...
I demand the floor!
Yes, it's your turn to speak.
Well, nuts to me.
I'm taking the stage.
I know the source of the greenhouse gases.
But in my shame, I've kept
it secret for 75 long years.
Oh, it haunts my memories still.
Professor, no! Don't do it!
Don't do what?
Don't use this memory ray
so I can remember what happened back then?
It was October 17th at 1:54 p.m.
and 14 birds were flying by the window.
I was working at
Mom's Friendly Robot Company.
Back then, you see,
robots were slow-moving, stiff
and a little on the uptight side.
Oh, dear.
Might I favor Master with
a tender kiss on the forehead?
Oh, I failed again.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
The owner of the company
pressured me
to create a bigger, sportier robot.
Stop! Oh!
It wasn't easy,
but by sacrificing fuel efficiency,
I succeeded.
What was that?
A flaming burp.
Does it always do that?
It's not always a burp.
We still have one problem, though.
This robot will never
meet emissions standards.
Crap spackle!
We'll just call it a Sport Utility Robot
and classify it as a light truck.
Well...
I suppose the environment
can take one more for the team.
What a fool I was!
If only I had made the effort
to develop a cleaner-burning robot.
But I was tired and in love.
Take me now, you stud!
Oh, this is all my fault!
That's awful, Professor.
Especially the making out part.
Yeah. I didn't need to hear that.
All modern robots descend
from my original smog-blasting designs,
and that's the cause
of global warming today.
Ah, so the robots are to blame,
as I suspected.
We are left with only one
possible course of action,
grim though it be.
I got a good feeling about this.
We must immediately and permanently
shut down, dismantle
and destroy all robots!
Wait. Surely there's a better...
The conference is over.
I must go now
to help collect cans on Jupiter.
Peace out, y'all.
Destroy all robots!
Poor Bender.
Be brave, my friend.
Oh.
Come on.
You've got to come out
of your chest sometime.
Would you do it for a Bender snack?
A-ha!
- Gotcha!
- Let me go!
I don't even want this stupid beer.
Yes!
You tried to trick me
into coming out of my chest,
but who has the beer now?
I've got mail.
Ooh.
It's a party, apparently.
Do you like to party?
To boogie down?
Well, I'm throwing an all-night
beach rager for my robot pals.
It all goes down this Saturday
on the isolated Galapagos Islands
where there will no escape...
From the fun!
All robots must attend.
Strange.
Why would Nixon, an awkward,
uncomfortable man,
suddenly throw a party,
one of the most social events imaginable?
It's a trap, is why!
They're going
to deactivate all the robots.
I don't hear any gasping.
We all figured that out.
Oh.
Well, I'm off.
Wait, we can hide you.
We'll pile fruit on you
and claim you're a bowl.
No. I'm going to the party.
I won't let you!
Fry, as you know,
there are lots of things
I'm willing to kill for.
Jewels, vengeance,
Father O'Malley's weed whacker.
But at long last I've found something
I'm willing to die for.
This mindless turtle.
Bender, this world isn't good
enough for you.
Not even close.
Goodbye, everybody!
Don't touch my stuff after I'm dead!
It's booby-trapped.
Do a little dance
Make a little love
Get down tonight
Do a little dance
Make a little love
Get down tonight
Poor guy.
Maybe you'd feel better if I had a drink.
Crummy keg.
It's completely...
Oh, you're a robot.
- Don't stop.
- Ew!
Attention, happening robots.
Who's got what it takes
to party with Nixon?
You fellows enjoy yourselves
for the next two hours
and be sure not to leave the island,
uh, for at least two hours.
I'm going out to pick up some smokes.
Really good smokes.
Two hours.
Okay, headless body of Agnew,
let's blow this joint.
Do you want to dance?
No, I'm not really in the...
You know you want to.
Per your orders,
I modified my mirror
to fire a colossal electromagnetic pulse
at the Galapagos.
Every robot will be instantly
and painfully terminated.
Now, for your part of the bargain?
Ah, ooh, very well.
Agnew, you belong to Wernstrom now.
I'll say goodbye now.
There ain't no turtles
where daddy's a-goin'.
Don't tell anybody, but Nixon's about
to shut all the robots off, and...
What!
- It's a trap.
- We're going to die.
Oh!
Nixon's not bringing the smokes.
Shut and pay attention to me, Bender!
Look, I love life and its pleasures
as much as anyone here,
except perhaps you, Hedonismbot.
But we need to be shut off!
Especially you, Hedonismbot.
I apologize for nothing!
We pollute too much!
We're destroying the world
and killing the turtles!
To hell with the turtles.
No one insults the turtles.
Come on, you...
Let the games begin!
Everyone, listen!
Damn!
I've devised a way to save you
and stop global warming at the same time.
Granted, you're all blasting out
greenhouse gases...
You're one to talk.
Ooh!
But we can use those
very gases to save the planet.
If you all vent your exhaust
directly upward in one burst,
it should thrust
the Earth further from the Sun,
thus cooling it.
By my calculations,
we'll need the full force
of every last robot.
So quickly,
everyone point your exhaust vents
straight upwards.
Now, vent.
Vent like the wind!
Harder! Harder!
Why isn't this working?
Some lazy or polite robot
is holding it in.
Help! Help!
A billion robot lives are
about to be extinguished!
Oh, the Jedis are going to feel this one!
I'm sorry, buddy.
At we'll die on our backs, helpless.
Huh?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, are you trying to make me look bad?
A-ha!
I'm even greater than I thought I was.
And now, to fulfill my destiny.
Fire!
- What the...
- We missed!
Professor, for saving the Earth
and foiling me,
I proudly, yet angrily, present you
with Earth's new highest honor,
the Polluting Medal of Pollution.
Thank you.
I deserve this.
Hey, Professor, now that the Earth's orbit
is further from the sun,
won't that make the year longer?
Why, yes.
One week longer, to be exact.
In that case I hereby declare it
Robot Party Week!
Me mind on fire
Me soul on fire feeling hot, hot, hot
Party people all around me
Feeling hot, hot, hot